# summary

Experienced public relations assistant with a demonstrated history of working in public relations and journalism industries. Strong community and social services professional skilled in Microsoft Word, editing, research, and press releases. Interested in front-end web development .

## education

#### **Kentucky State University**

#### Bachelor's Degree, Mass Communications, Print Journalism

Frankfort, Kentucky

Graduated May 2017

Graduated Magna Cum Laude. Editor in Chief for Thorobred News, KSU's student-run newspaper, during 2016-2017 academic year; previously opinions editor and staff writer. Worked in tutoring department with a focus on English and Journalism studies.

# employment history

## McCracken County Public Library

#### **Library Clerk**

Paducah, Kentucky

August 2018 - Present

Routine clerical work involving basic support services and services to patrons, with a focus on giving patrons a unique and positive experience.

Responsible for routine circulation, shelf maintenance and clerical functions using automated circulation system. This position includes making beginning level library clerical decisions. The work requires knowledge, skill and ability in library clerical functions, as well as customer/patron service.

## City of Frankfort, KY

#### **Public Relations Assistant**

Frankfort, Kentucky

June 2016 - January 2018

Worked under the grants/public relations manager, Rebecca Hall. Crafted and distributed press releases for multiple departments within City Management. Collated information for grants projects and created presentations. Interviewed local city leaders and employees for press releases, quarterly newsletters, and biweekly employee newsletters.

Many of my press releases were published, and the presentations I helped assemble found themselves in Washington, D.C., and in front of local politicians.

Work samples available upon request.

#### Thorobred News, Kentucky State University

#### **Editor in Chief**

Frankfort, Kentucky

June 2016 - May 2017

Worked with staff to provide timely and relevant news to Kentucky State University's student body. Managed a sizable student staff, providing editing and directional assistance when needed.

Laid out newspaper in Adobe InDesign and Photoshop. Communicated with local newspaper to print Thorobred News.

Thorobred News' goal in the 2016-2017 academic year was to stabilize a timely publication, provide more hard news, and allow the university community to contribute to their newspaper if they so desired. With the help of a dedicated staff, Thorobred News was able to achieve all of these goals.

Work samples available upon request.

# hobbies & interests

I'm an avid reader, news consumer, knitter, and front-end web development learner. I'm interested in history, humanities, and how people today can use these things to make the world a better place for all.

# professional skills

Word processor
Editing
Research
Teamwork
Problem Solving
Microsoft Suite
Leadership Skills
Public Speaking
Adobe Indesign
HTML

**Public Relations** 



# languages

English German

**CSS** 

Native Conversational

# references

## Rebecca Hall

Former Supervisor

## Lacey Trautwein

Colleague

## David Shabazz

Kentucky State University Journalism Professor